runtime.org 2007-08-27

# Data Recovery Software - File System Utilities

## Privacy Statement & Refund Policy 

#####  Use of Personal Information 

Runtime Software may store and process personal information in order to better understand our customers' needs, and therefore provide improved products and services. We may use your personal information to contact you about new products or promotional campaigns. Your personal information could also be used to contact you in instances of difficulty processing or shipping your order.

Your personal information is not shared with anyone outside of Runtime Software. 

##### Security 

We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. 

Runtime Software is committed to keeping your personal data safe and we take every reasonable precaution to ensure security. Access to your personal information is restricted to the employees at Runtime Software. Our employees are required to maintain the confidentiality of this information, and may not use this data for any purpose other than to complete the services required of their employment. Your personal data is used for internal purposes only and is never sold or shared with anyone outside of Runtime Software, unless we disclose information in response to a law enforcement request. 

##### Use of Cookies 

We might use cookies, small pieces of data stored on the user's hard drive, to track time and pages you have visited. If you feel uncomfortable about this you can switch off the acceptance of cookies in your browser options. With cookies switched off, you still can use all features of our web site, including the online order form. 

##### Refund Policy 

Please download, install, and trial the demo version of the software before ordering. Help is always available through our Support Department ([support@runtime.org](mailto:support@runtime.org)) if you encounter any difficulties or have questions. We are willing to work with our customers until the problem is solved.

Orders can be cancelled prior to program registration, no fees applicable.

After software registration codes are issued, we regret we are unable to issue refunds.
